{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935142175","data":{"timestamp":" 946935142175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935146482","data":{"timestamp":" 946935146481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935153566","data":{"timestamp":" 946935153566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935208699","data":{"timestamp":" 946935208698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935214765","data":{"timestamp":" 946935214765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935215835","data":{"timestamp":" 946935215835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935221498","data":{"timestamp":" 946935221498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935230371","data":{"timestamp":" 946935230371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935289831","data":{"timestamp":" 946935289831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935338894","data":{"timestamp":" 946935338894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.na.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946935350702","data":{"timestamp":" 946935350701"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_003113"," gameId":" 42a343ef-3e85-4a56-b38b-6475cea6615f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.na.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_na__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}